[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 8, "question": "Who thinks sex is bad?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "VBP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 9, "answer": "Not me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "WRB", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 63, "question": "Penn Jillette, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "Oh, why I -- I'm just so excited to have Rush and sex below my picture --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Penn Jillette"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "What is the concept then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "The concept is that sex is bad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "Well, who thinks sex is bad?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "Not me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Yes, I agree --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "JJ", "VBZ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "-- when you -- when you take religion to its extremities?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WRB", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "Well, I -- I actually think that this does certainly -- anti-sex does start often in religion.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "You would?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "How many times he has sex.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "You would?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "EX", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "Once you've said sex is a bad thing -- doesn't all of this follow logically?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "But there can't be anybody in the world who genuinely thinks sex is a bad thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "That it's a bad thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "Or a bad thing outside of wedlock?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "Well, sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "It's one of the great wonders of the world, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "RB", "RB", "RB", "TO", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "As an atheist, when you see that happening politically, and these are people who may one day be your president -- what do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "RB", ",", "CC", "DT", "VBP", "NNS", "WP", "MD", "CD", "NN", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "Well, you have to -- it's very, very hard not to just be told you so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "Are there elements of a religious conviction which you think could be helpful to somebody as a political leader?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "You have to have the passion for freedom greater than the passion for you know what's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "Can I join you here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "Yes, you may.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "But the better way for America to go now is to collectively put all this brain power together and think, how do we keep this country where it should be, a great country?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "CC", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "I think that I always go with individualism.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "What has gone wrong with the American Dream?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "You know, I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 345, "question": "So, Kal, what's more fun -- working with Hugh Laurie on \"House,\" being in a hit movie, or running in the corridors of power with the president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "JJR", "JJ", ":", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "``", "NNP", ",", "''", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "Probably different kinds of fun, I would say.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kal", "Hugh Laurie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "If I held a metaphorical bullet to your head and you could only do one of these things the rest of your life -- movies, TV, politics?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "NNS", ",", "NN", ",", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "I would get rid of TV and I would choose between movies and politics.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "CD", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "Which one is it going to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "CD", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "One is fact and one is fiction.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "Would you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "Because you're helping real people with real substantive things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "What's it been like in there to be at the center of things looking out with everybody else wondering what's going on in there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "EX", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "It's been pretty remarkable.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "What would you say are the common misconceptions about the president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "Oh, gosh.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Do you accept that as a criticism?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "No, I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "ORGAN: What kind of guy is he when the door shuts?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "The same.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "PRP", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "Who would you most like to come up against?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "RBS", "IN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "To me, all of the candidates are the same, just in terms of the policy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "You're a busy guy, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "I try to keep busy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "What is rotten, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "Well, I have a -- I'm a father of six children.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "If I asked you, for example, what your view of gay marriage is, what would you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "Go ahead and ask me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["August"], "PERSON": ["Christine O'Donnell"]}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "What is your view of gay marriage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "I feel like I just got imported into the Christine O'Donnell interview you did back in August.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "Would you tell them that gay marriage is a sin?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "I would tell my children, as -- I tell them what I believe myself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "What do you believe?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "I believe that marriage was defined by God a long time ago.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "Do you think homosexuality is a sin?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "I think that it's -- it's unnatural.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "So what's your view of abortion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "POS", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "I think that it's wrong.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "Under any circumstances?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "Under any circumstances.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 621, "question": "Even rape and incest?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 622, "answer": "I think someone who is ultimately willing to murder a child, even to fix another tragic end, a devastating situation like rape or incest or things like that, is not taking the moral high road.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 624, "question": "Could you honestly look a daughter in the eye if she was raped and say you have got to have that child?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 625, "answer": "AMERON: Yes, and I will help you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 626, "question": "You would do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 627, "answer": "Yes, of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 668, "question": "Whose do you take?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 669, "answer": "I take my values.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]